I can be many things,
but I'm not the enemy
of the person she loves the most.
It's Mikoy. I think I know
where to find him.
He is in Hong Kong.
How can you say that, and how
did you come up with that theory?
It's available exclusively
in pharmacies in Hong Kong.
From now on, don't worry about me.
That you have to protect me.
From now on,
I'll be the one who will protect you.
We have a solid lead on Chiara and Mikoy.
- Alex is in Hong Kong?!
- Yes, sir.
Sir, ma'am.
I picked up some information
from down below.
From down below? Nothing from up above?
Ma'am, we're a syndicate.
Spill the tea. Come on, spill it.
He said spill it already.
And what exactly is CHENES?
You know I don't believe
the acronyms you make up.
No, ma'am, this one's legit.
A Cross-border Enforcement Network
for Extradition and Surveillance.
Sir, they only use that when there's
coordinated law enforcement in Hong Kong.
Do we have someone there?
I already called our vendor.
Vendor?
Ma'am, you need to keep up with the terms.
Of course, a "criminal affiliate".
Can you see something we can't?
It's just us here, right?
The line is quiet.
But I have a very strong feeling.
This Code Red.
It's for Mikoy and Chiara.
Is he here?
Is Mikoy here?
Is Chiara with him?
Yes.
You know I can't help them.
We're talking about my son, Norberto.
After everything I've done for you,
this is how you'll repay me?
Well.
I know a way
for them to escape to Hong Kong.
They will have to take
a private vehicle to Mindanao.
After that,
a private boat to Borneo.
And from Borneo,
they can fly to Hong Kong.
Look.
Gun control is strict there.
Inter-agency coordination is strong.
But you know what that means.
Mikoy will be branded
a traitor to the agency.
And you'll hunt him down.
Yes, as a matter of procedure.
Assets who turned away from the agency,
who handled sensitive information,
are considered a threat.
Leave everything behind.
We have to go now!
Wait a second, sweetheart.
Can you at least tell me
what's really going on?
Because that taxi
that was following me earlier.
It's parked right outside now.
And?
Why would it park there during rush hour?
Maybe he's waiting for a passenger.
There are so many taxis in Hong Kong.
Maybe the driver lives here.
Or it broke down. Like that.
And I heard our neighbor,
Jing, lost her dog.
Hocco?
I knew it. It was Hocco. Definitely Hocco.
You know,
maybe he's just out with his dog buddies.
- You know, just hanging out.
- Mikoy!
- What?
- Just listen to me.
Something is happening,
and we need to leave now!
Sweetheart.
You know, maybe you're just hungry.
You know, let's just go eat
some real duck,
because I don't like Peking duck, okay?
Come on.
It's too late.
- Why?
- They've already found us.
Sweetheart.
Are you sure you're okay in there?
Isn't it a little too cramped?
Actually, I think it's perfect.
Perfect?
Yes.
If we ever find a way out,
the hallways are narrow,
so they won't be able
to rush us all at once.
One at a time.
We can take them out one at a time.
You know, sweetheart,
you're really scary.
But at the same time,
you're really hot too.
- Good thing you're with me.
- Come on.
Enough talking. Open the door already.
Okay.
I've missed this.
Let's go.
What is this?!
This mustache is so itchy!
We really need
these disguises, sweetheart.
To keep us safe.
Just hang in there, sweetheart.
I know.
I've been putting up with this
for a while now.
Come on! Let's go!
All right, all right.
I'm just using the restroom.
That's what I thought.
Are you ready?
I'll go first.
Clear.
You're so hot, sweetheart!
Let's go!
…Is equals to…
Then Y was 3…
Mario, here's your water.
- Thank you.
- Get up.
Look at your son.
Look at him.
He's enjoying math.
Doing it for fun
while on vacation.
Isn't that a good thing?
How is that a good thing?
That's not normal behavior for a kid.
He's way too hardworking.
Wrong.
You're right.
That's concerning.
I can hear you, you know.
He's on high alert now.
This is getting dangerous.
Maybe we should kick him
out of this house already.
Kick out?
Come here. We're saving you.
- From what?
- From maths.
Honestly, I think you're
more dangerous than his math.
- Wow, Bechay, where's the support?
- Bechay, stop it.
Don't talk back. Support us instead.
And we need to get this kid some sunlight.
Too smart and too hardworking!
I've heard about people like that.
They need to touch grass. Like that.
Kids like that need to be grounded.
Surprise!
Captain Pepe!
Someone is looking for Angelito.
Who?
Sofie?
Hey! We have a visitor. Hello!
Hey. What are you doing here?
Son, don't be like that!
She came all the way to see you.
That means my son is worth visiting.
So many questions!
Why don't you invite her inside
for some juice?
It's such a hot day!
Meanwhile, you're making me
stay outside in this heat.
Enough questions. Go on.
Come over here.
How have you been?
How's your father?
Does he know you're here?
Actually, I'd like to apply
to your bakery.
Huh?
Mamma Mia!
‪My God.
Oh, no.
Let's go, let's go.
Hurry!
Quickly!
Yes. That's definitely Mikoy.
Yes! You're really something, Brusko.
Boom, roasted! Boom boom.
By the way you're dancing,
I assume it's good news.
They've found Mikoy and Chiara.
So it's confirmed? They're in Hong Kong?
Absolutely confirmed, sir.
You know, I'm really impressed
with your daughter.
She actually went to a place
where La Morte Bianca has no influence.
And that's not all.
There are gun restrictions too.
Boom, roasted! Boom boom, roasted.
Who helped them?
I don't care
which Pontius Pilate helped them.
I wouldn't even be surprised
if it were a senator.
Kidding aside, what's important is,
are they safe
from the reach of La Morte Bianca?
We know too well that nobody's safe
from La Morte Bianca.
There's reportedly a disturbance
in the Tsim Sha Tsui area.
Chiara!
Giancarlo de Luca?
He's not a De Luca.
His name is Donatello Belladonna.
The Painter.
It would be stupid of me not to,
because I'd die
if I were to face you without one.
Mikoy, go on ahead.
I'll handle this.
Let me handle this first, Chiara.
Let me take down Giancarlo.
The Painter, Il Terrazo.
I can't hit you, okay?
And I'll never hit you, sweetheart.
Come on. Show me what you can do.
No way!
I really can't do that, okay?
And I could never hurt
the woman I love. Never.
Sweetheart!
The violence!
That hurt!
Sweetheart, I know you love me.
I know that, and I love you very much too.
But this is a dangerous world we live in.
And I'm sure you know that by now.
So please indulge me.
I need to prepare you.
And I need to believe
that you can handle yourself
and that I can also rely on you.
So, come on.
Fair enough.
I've already been trained
by Agent Alex at the agency.
Who?
Agent Alex.
Ouch.
See?
All you learned was basic useless stuff
that won't even be useful
in the real world.
Okay.
Because in the real world, sweetheart,
there's no fighting stance.
There's no time for that.
And you shouldn't immediately reveal
what your next move is.
Okay.
And you need to fight fast.
It has to be efficient
and as dirty as you can.
You're so dirty.
The dirtier, the better.
Because in a real fight,
every part of the body is fair game.
You won't have time to prepare
for their attacks
because they won't announce them.
Okay. Tap, sweetheart.
Okay.
Your training style is intense.
It feels like a near-death experience.
- Okay.
- Stand up!
Il Pittore.
Teenage Mutant Donatello.
- Chiara, let me handle this first.
- Mikoy.
So you can't use it anymore.
Even if my hand is cut,
I can still kill you.
What's that?
That was unfair.
Sorry.
Someone just taught me that.
But in a real fight,
every part of the body is fair game.
Okay.
Come on.
I can handle this.
Trust me.
- Your turn.
- Okay.
Not like that.
- Why?
- Left foot forward.
Wrong. Use your left hand.
- Okay.
- What, one more?
No, that's enough.
Well done.
This is a bespoke jacket.
Back off over here.
Let the duel continue.
- Harry Potter?
- No.
Harry Painter.
Mikoy!
You want to me to go home already?
What a shame, I have
a valuable update about your brother.
You really do not want to know
the update about your brother?
All right, I'll just go.
Okay, fine, tell me the update.
- Fun time is over. Let's go!
- Hey!
Don't move!
Put your hands up.
Agent Alex.
I missed you.
I told you, put your hands up! All of you!
- There you go.
- Okay.
We're not friends, Mikoy.